>> Kyle Simpson: 我一直在为胁迫而做一件事情，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: As I've been making this
case for coercion, one of the things that
可能是在你脑海中飘浮的
may have been floating in the back of
your mind is, yeah, but the coercion
我没有与加号运算符或 if 语句的问题。
problem that I have is not with
the plus operator, or an if statement.
大多数人认为的大胁迫问题
The big coercion problems
that most people seem to have
似乎是平等检查的中心
seem to center around equality checking.
而我对所有胁迫所传达的信息也同样适用
And the same message that I have for
all of coercion is going to apply for
强制性的平等。
coercive equality as well.
但我想具体去想一些关于 == 和 ===的问题，
But I wanna dig specifically into
some issues about the == versus ===,
因为这才是大多数人关注的地方
since this is really the place where
most people focus their attention
当他们谈论胁迫的时候
when they talk about coercion.
其实大多数人都没有想到过胁迫
In fact most people haven't thought
about coercion any other place
== = == = 。
other than the == verse the ===.
所以有更多的解剖
So there's some further dissection.
那么你们有多少人之前听说过 == 和
So how many of you have heard before
that the difference between == and
=== 是 == 检查所谓的宽松的等同性的值
=== is that == checks the value so
called loose equality and
=== 检查类型中的值，称为严格等同性?
=== checks the value in the type so
called strict equality?
这是非常普遍的。
This is extremely common.
不幸的是，虽然听起来很不错，但这并不是完全正确的。
And unfortunately even though it sounds
really good it's not exactly the case.
这不是什么区别
That's not exactly the difference.
这不仅仅是一个学术上的细微差别。
And it's not just an academic nuance here.
区别真的改变了我们对公用事业的看法
The difference really changes
our perspective on the utility,
这两种机制的目的。
the purpose of these two
mechanisms in our language.
所以我真的觉得如果你想了解你的代码
So, I really think that if you're
trying to understand your code,
重要的是你学会像 JavaScript一样思考
it's critical that you learn
to think like JavaScript,
这就是这篇论文的主题
that's sort of been
the thesis going along.
双等性和三重平等是一样的
And the same is true for double equals and
triple equals, that just saying,
这好像是在检查类型而另一个则不检查
well, it's sort of one seems to check
the type and the other doesn't.
这可能会让你在某些情况下得到你的支持
That may get you by in some circumstances,
but
在其他情况下它会导致你完全不同的结论
in other circumstances it leads you
to completely different conclusions.
和我们所做的所有事情都是一致的，让我们看看这个规范。
So consistent with everything else that
we've done, let's look at the spec.
这是以下的规范 :
This is the spec for
所谓抽象等同性比较，就是双等号。
what is called abstract equality
comparison, which is the double equals.
如果双等号只检查值和三重值，那么检查值和
And if double equals only checks the value
and triple equals checks the value and
那么在算法的最上面写的是什么
the type, then why write up here
at the very top of the algorithm,
非常快速的是 X 型和 Y 型检查吗
the very fast thing,
are the types of x and y checked?
我们马上就能揭穿这个神话
Immediately we can debunk the myth
两者的区别在于类型是否相同。
that the difference between these two
is whether the types are the same.
那不是区别
That isn't the difference.
他们都检查过类型只是
They both checked the types,
it's just that
跟其他的信息有什么区别
one does something different with that
information than the other one, okay?
第一，真理的来源始终如我们所说的。
So number 1, the source of truth is
always the spec, as we keep saying.
如果你选择不完全正确的心理模型
And if you choose to persist in not
completely correct mental models
在某些情况下，最终的时间跨度越长，
that seem to work in some scenarios,
eventually the longer the time span goes,
最终你会出现在一个不同的场景中
eventually you'll run into a case
where you're in a different scenario,
你的精神模型已经被破坏了现在你迷路了
your mental model is busted,
and now you're lost.
我觉得最好有一个正确的精神模型
I think it's better to have
the correct mental model.
就像我为你说的那个规格的其他地方
Just like the other places of the spec
that I have cited for you, this is
具有 if 语句和语句以及变量和操作的算法。
an algorithm with if statements and then
statements and variables and operations.
所以你作为一个开发者可以理解的东西。
So it's something that you as
a developer can understand.
绝大多数 JavaScript 开发者从未阅读过此部分。
The vast majority of JavaScript developers
have never once read this section.
他们听说过的都是平等的
All they've ever heard about
the double equals is what is said
在网上约双等号和两双平等的书
online about double equals and
in books about double equals.
这几乎从来没有提到过什么规格的谈判。
Which is almost never citing
what the spec talks about.
但只提到一些轶事证据，他们认为这是值得的。
But only citing some anecdotal
evidence why they think it's worthy.
所以阅读这个规范是有用的。
So reading the spec can be useful.
例如，如果我有一个字符串， Frank，我已分配给一个变量，并且
For example, if I have a string, Frank,
that I've assigned to one variable, and
然后我创造了另一个拷贝基本上就是第 2 行上的情况
then I create another copy, essentially,
that's what's happening on line 2,
所以现在我有两条绳子
so now I have two strings.
如果在第 7 行，我尝试问这两者是否相等，就像我在第 7 行和第 8 行一样。
And if on line 7 I try to ask if those two
are equal, like I am on line 7 and line 8.
在这两种情况下，它们是平等的。
In both cases, they are equal.
因为事实证明，当类型匹配时，它们会执行 ===。
Because it turns out that when
the types match, then they do the ===.
双等号和
The double equals and
当类型匹配时，三重等号完全相同。
the triple equals are exactly
identical when the types match.
完全没有差别。
There is absolutely no difference.
而且这个规格是这样说的
And the spec says so.
当类型匹配时，请执行三重等号。
When the types match,
do the triple equals.
这就是我刚为你强调的
That's what I just highlighted for you.
我们可以在代码中看到它。
And we can see that in code.
在任何位置中，值类型已匹配，并且方式为 I
In any place where the value types
already match, and by the way, as I
已经说过好几次了，你应该试着把值的类型确定，
said a bunch of times already, you should
try to have the value types obvious, and
理想情况下，应尽可能让它们匹配。
ideally, you should have them
matching as much as possible.
但这并不意味着你永远不能进行胁迫
That doesn't mean you can
never have coercion, but
你不应该有很多地方做比较
you shouldn't have lots of places
where you're doing comparisons.
你肯定不应该做平等比较
You certainly shouldn't be
doing equality comparisons and
完全不知道这些类型是什么
have absolutely no idea
what the types are.
我很有趣的是很多人似乎认为
It's interesting to me that many people
seem to suggest that it is impossible for
他们将会进行编程并了解到这一比较可能有哪些类型。
them to program and understand what types
could be coming in to this comparison.
我不知道你怎么能写出任何算法
And I don't know how you can write any
algorithm without having some sense of
这些都是数字这些都是字符串
well these are always numbers and
these are always strings.
你怎么能说我不知道呢
How can you say, well I have no idea?
它可能是一个数组，它可能为空。
It could be an array it could be null.
我不知道它可能是什么
I have no idea what it could possibly be.
即使你不知道，这并不意味着它必须保持这种状态。
And even if you don't know, that doesn't
mean that it has to stay that way.
您可以选择重新设计代码
You can choose to redesign your code so
你缩小了那些不同种类的地方
that you've narrowed the surface area
of places where those different kinds
类型可以相互交织，可以相互交织。
of types can intermatch,
can interweave with each other.
你缩小了那些以胁迫方式存在的角落
You've narrowed those corner
cases that exist with coercion.
所以我就不会写一个函数可以是空的，没有定义的字符串，
So I wouldn't write a function that
could take null, undefined string,
数字，对象，数组和其他 14 种类型，以及
number, object, array,
and 14 other types, and
然后把他们跟一个 ==，那个很可笑，对吧 ?
then all compare them with a ==,
that's ludicy, right?
但我会写一个函数可以带弦和数字
But I would write a function that
could take strings and numbers and
请将其与 ==进行比较。
compare them with a ==.
因为有一个非常有名的
Because there's a very known and
可能发生的转角型个案的小子集。
small subset of potential
corner cases to work around.
如果你注意的话这些都是可以避免的
And those are avoidable
if you pay attention.
因此，在类型已匹配的情况下， == 和 === 相同。
So in the case where the types already
match, == and === are the same.
那 === 什么
So what is === doing?
它也在检查这些类型，如果它们不一样，它是错误的。
Well, it's also checking the types, and
if they're not the same, it's false.
不管这些价值是什么
It doesn't matter what the values are,
如果类型不同，它不会执行任何其他操作。
if the types are different,
it doesn't do anything else.
它 sorta 短路说
It sorta short-circuits and says,
如果类型不同，那么它们不可能相等。
if the types are different there's no
possible way that they could be equal.
如果你想的是什么是双重平等
If you think about that with respect
to what double equals is gonna do,
我们马上就能看到了
which we're gonna look
at in just a moment.
本质上严格的平等和
Essentially the real difference
between strict equality and
宽松的平等是我们是否要允许任何胁迫发生。
loose equality is whether or not we're
going to to allow any coercion to occur.
那么，如果类型相同，我们严格的 " 平等 " 会做什么 ?
So what us Strict Equality is gonna
do if the types are the same?
如果他们是 NaN的话就会返回 false
Well it's going to,
return false if they're NaNs,
因为记得那是关于 Nafe 的事
because remember it's
supposed to lie about NaNs.
如果有负零点就会返回真实情况因为它应该是谎言
And it's gonna return true if there's a
negative zero because it's supposed to lie
关于零的零
about negative zeros.
但只有在类型已经匹配的情况下才会有谎言。
But it only does the lies
if the types already match.
否则，它说假话，什么都没看。
Otherwise, it says false and
it didn't check anything at all.
也许更合适的说法是
So maybe the more appropriate
statement would be
他们俩都检查过其中的一处都停了一处就没了
that they both check the types one of
them stops early and one of them doesn't.
或者说不一样，区别在于我们是否允许胁迫。
Or said a different way, the difference
is whether we allow coercion.
所以我有两个对象，好吗 ?
So here, I have two objects, all right?
它们具有相同的结构，表面上是相同的值。
They have the same structure and
ostensibly the same value.
但它们不是同一个对象。
But they are not the same object.
它们是两个不同的对象。
They are two different objects.
很多时候人们迷上了用 JavaScript 构建的平等检查
A lot of times people get confused with
JavaScript's built in equality checking
它在某种程度上不是结构上的
that it's somehow not
structural in nature,
它不像一个有深度的断言
that it doesn't do like
a deep assertion check that
一个对象的结构与另一个对象的结构完全相同。
the structure of one object is exactly
the same as a structure of another object.
可能有这样的语言，但是我不知道
Maybe there are languages like that,
but I don't know
它是一种以语言为基础的主流事物。
of that to be a prevailing thing that's
built into an operator in a language.
大多数运算符似乎执行 JavaScript 执行的操作，即身份比较。
Most operators seem to do what JavaScript
does, which is identity comparison.
如果 workshop1 和worksh坊 2 完全指向同一对象引用，那么
If workshop1 and workshop 2 pointed at
literally the same object reference then
他们的身份是一样的你会得到真实的
their identity would be the same and
you'd get true.
但在这个特定情况下，它们不相等，好吗 ?
But in this particular case,
they're not equal, okay?
因此， == 和 === 不会返回 true ，因为它们是不同的对象。
So neither == nor === is gonna return
a true because they are different objects.
所有人都跟着我吗
Everybody follow me?
它们是不同的物体，它们不一样。
They're different objects,
they are not the same.
所以不管你用哪一个
And so
it doesn't matter which one you use,
你还是会得到同样的结果
you're still gonna get the same result.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 换句话说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So in other words,
当类型不同时， == 将允许进行强制。
the == is going to allow coercion
when the types were different.
当类型相同时， === 将不允许进行强制。
And the === is going to disallow
coercion when the types are the same.